{
    "id": "ebf6f4ad81d841f4b97b093c5bdb1ffe",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I was late because my car ……………… on the way to work.",
            "description": "When something breaks down, it stops functioning.",
            "answers": [
                "broke up",
                "broke down",
                "broke off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "20cff4e9354440c1b61961e8722bb360"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………. with her best friend when he lied to her.",
            "description": "To break up with somebody is to end your relationship with them.",
            "answers": [
                "broke up",
                "broke off",
                "broke down"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "845e498cf46142cf80e7d8812ea6fb71"
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl ………………………. when she heard that she had failed.",
            "description": "To break down is to lose control of your emotions.",
            "answers": [
                "broke off",
                "broke down",
                "broke out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a13b2a17abaa49f391de88d89f6a560e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The warden …………………….. our conversation.",
            "description": "To break in on is to interrupt.",
            "answers": [
                "broke in on",
                "broke up on",
                "broke out on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e76fe8d47aa141ceb2b084d204e86737"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cholera …………………… after the floods.",
            "description": "When a disease breaks out, it appears and spreads suddenly.",
            "answers": [
                "broke up",
                "broke out",
                "broke off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5b1abfb7d74d42f4bf8015d159c55b91"
        },
        {
            "question": "A dangerous prisoner ………………………. the high security prison yesterday.",
            "description": "To break out of jail is to escape from captivity.",
            "answers": [
                "broke out of",
                "broke up of",
                "broke off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f8dbbb00a8b848209a9af4469c3d5ad0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please …………………….. your coat. It is very cold.",
            "description": "To put on coat is to wear it.",
            "answers": [
                "put on",
                "put off",
                "try on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4d05f76d28dc4a05997c555af6174843"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind if I ……………………. TV? I would like to watch the match.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "turned up",
                "turned on",
                "turned in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "08fbf02bb7f048a28543b9bfccbedf47"
        },
        {
            "question": "Excuse me. Where can I …………………….. the shirt?",
            "description": "To try on a shirt is to try wearing it to see if it fits you.",
            "answers": [
                "try in",
                "try out",
                "try on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "edbf26c3f7d44038b0264790257182db"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you don’t …………………….. the train now, it will leave without you.",
            "description": "To get on the train is to board it.",
            "answers": [
                "get in",
                "get on",
                "get up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "afa03f7ca4ea4b2d9501f0f2b68f53fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can I ……………………… working now?",
            "description": "To carry on something is to continue doing it.",
            "answers": [
                "carry out",
                "carry on",
                "carry in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d8f66f8120574ea3b2738d57bab62bbd"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must …………………….. smoking.",
            "description": "To give up smoking is to quit it.",
            "answers": [
                "give up",
                "give in",
                "give out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f4fe9cc9d60f43cea5cf6d951706fc9c"
        }
    ]
}